http://www.atlantixglobal.com/privacy-policy/

Use Of Cookies
©1999 - 2020 CXtec Inc.
CXtec hosts the website www.cxtec.com at its world headquarters, located at 5404 South Bay Road,  Syracuse, NY 13221-4799. We can be reached by phone at 315.476.3000. Inquiries about the website should be directed to service@cxtec.com.
Legal Disclaimer
The information, text, graphics and links provided on www.cxtec.com are provided by CXtec as a convenience to its customers. CXtec is not responsible for the accuracy, timeliness or completeness of the information, text, graphics, links or other items housed on this server. However, CXtec retains copyrights to all images, graphics and text, unless otherwise noted. Users may not distribute, mirror, or modify and reuse any copyrighted text, graphics or images on this website for commercial purposes without written consent from CXtec or the copyright holder. Users may print copies of the information, store information and reference information from this server for your own personal use. CXtec reserves all rights to this website. Products featured on these websites are trademarks of their respective companies and their likeness may not be replicated without the manufacturer's permission.
CXtec is the owner of the following trademarks and/or service marks: CABLExpress®, CXtec®, CXtec Dinosaurs®, equal2new®, Performance Guaranteed Technology Equipment™, Technology @ Your Pace®, Skinny-Trunk®, RapidCare®, LIFECYCLExpress®, Green Cube®, Respect Layer One®, We make your network…..work®,  CABLExpress EXP Series®, Z-Mount®, and Know Your Source®.
Cables for a Cure® is a registered mark of Susan G. Komen for a Cure, used under license.
CABLE TALK® is a registered mark of CableTalk Systems Inc., used under license.
All other trademarks are property of their respective owners.
©1999 - 2017 CXtec Inc. All rights reserved.
Back to top
Back to top
Privacy Policy
When visiting this website, information about your browser type, operating system, IP address, and the domain from which you came is collected. We do not collect any personally identifiable information unless you submit it (Personally identifiable information includes names, postal addresses, e-mail addresses, phone numbers, banking and billing information, account information, credit card numbers or any other combination of data that could be used to identify you including, but not limited to your birthdate, zip code, gender). Any personally identifiable information that you give us will only be used to respond to you and will not be retained, unless you submit the information as an application (i.e. online credit application, e-newsletter subscription request). Any information that we do collect from the visitor's home server is only used in aggregate to determine whether improvements can be made in our service and is discarded. Parties who communicate with CXtec via e-mail may receive future communications by e-mail. If you receive e-mail and wish to be removed from our distribution list, please contact us at removeme@cxtec.com. Parties who submit their postal addresses to request marketing materials or company information will be added to our mailing lists to ensure that they receive future mailings. If you wish to be removed from our mailing list, clip the address label from the literature you received and submit it in care of the marketing department to the address listed above. CXtec respects the privacy of its customers and pledges to protect their privacy by not sharing e-mail addresses with any third-party groups. You can remove your address from this list at anytime by sending an email to removeme@cxtec.com.
To opt out of targeted advertising, please go here: https://www.cxtec.com/unsubscribe-form/
Back to top
Back to top
Use of Cookies
Any information collected is stored using a cookie that is placed on your computer. We do NOT use this cookie to collect or store personally identifiable information about you. However, the cookie is used to track information about how you interact with our website. It also allows our website to be customized to meet your interests.
Back to top
Back to top
